a very very interesting experience.
It was all the emotions. A lot of a lot
of fun, a lot of nerves,
but
all in all it was cool to experience it
for the first time and I'm just I'm so
grateful to be back home.
Did you hear anything throughout this
process from other teams about maybe
either what more they would
or do you feel like there's more like
hey, this is what else I have to prove?
I think most importantly as a player I
believe that I'm I'm just scratching the
surface of of what I can be.
And
there's
I personally would just always be
looking for ways that I can individually
improve and so it wasn't more so it
wasn't more so much what like
any other team
had to say or
it really wasn't anything negative. But
I'm just excited to
keep getting more opportunities and keep
on my keep putting my best foot forward.
Nikki.
Hi Chris, congratulations.
So did you did you have offers from
other teams and
you know what ultimately led you back to
Washington? Why did you want to come
back here?
Absolutely.
I've always said that I'm an inaugural
commander
and it was kind of cool to be in the
draft class that was here when we
sort of rebranded and so
um
this organization just has a lot of
sentimental value to me. So as many
offers that may have been received from
other teams I knew that
in any event I would be leaning towards
being a commander.
Donna.
Hi Chris, welcome back and
congratulations.
Learn and Tunsil talked about you this
week when we heard from him. He said
that you were easy to be with in the
locker room and that you were a plus in
the locker room and for this team. Could
you talk a little bit about your
teammate talking about how important you
are to have back?
Um it's
it's the biggest honor and I think
as a player
what your teammates, what your brothers
have to say about you is like the
biggest honor and
the the biggest judgment you could
probably ever receive in this league and
I definitely appreciate his his his kind
words and I he knows cuz I've told him
personally
how much of an honor it is to have him
in this building and how much of an
honor it is to play next to him. And so
I'm I'm just really really really really
excited and really honored to to be back
with my brothers.
And getting the opportunity to start
early last season, how did you see
yourself as far as your growth? What was
the biggest growth that you saw in
yourself throughout last year?
Yeah, I definitely I just saw a lot of
growth
in just becoming a leader. I saw a lot
of growth in my communication and I saw
a lot of growth in just my confidence in
how to communicate and making sure
I take pride in
knowing that we're all on the same page
and I take
I take pride in just being confident out
there and knowing that I can complete
the task at hand. So I think I just took
a lot of strides
in all of those aspects.
Congratulations again. Thank you, Donna.
Ben.
Hey Chris, welcome back.
Obviously one big change since you've
been since the end of the year is
new coordinator, new plan. What's your
sense of
what what this new look with David
Blough may mean for you in terms of
blocking and how do you prepare for that
this off season? Absolutely. I'm I'm
super excited for coach Blough and
um
and I just
I just
am happy to just see the offense that
he's going to assemble and
it's it's going to be great and I sort
of have an idea
um
or a slight idea of the scheme and what
everything will look like and I'm just
excited to
even meet with my coaches this week and
continuously to get up to speed as we
head into the off season program.
And you know obviously you started the
last 15 games last year today
Punt coming back does that say anything
about the role? Are you still the
starter or how do they
label that as to you as to what may
happen next?
Um they've said nothing about that and
what I know about this organization is
um
where we are all about competition.
Competition, competition, competition
and that's all they emphasize and so
that is the mindset
heading into
to everything. So.
Awesome. Thank you, Chris.
Does anyone else have any more
questions? Hey, can I ask him one more?
Yeah, one more. Darnell Elkins getting
the head the job that the offensive line
coach. What what do you think about
Darnell and the job that he's done and
what is that what do you think about him
ascending to that role?
Man, I'm just I'm so happy for coach
Tape and
I don't know that there's someone out
there more deserving. Um and I just know
that our room is absolutely just going
to
rally and galvanize around him
he just brings a
an energy
a passion and confidence to the game
that I know that we're all excited to be
a part of and buy into and he's going to
do a great job.
Good. Everyone good?